

ARIEL LARA PEDRAZA

Computer Systems Engineering Student Cybersecurity

PERSONAL INFORMATION

I'm a 22 years old Computer Systems Engineer Student at Instituto Tecnológico de Morelia in México, coursing my 9th semester. I'm working as a FullStack Developer at IINII and Stardeos (standby). I consider myself as a extremelly curious person and I'm always ready to give my best. Hoping to join an International Residences Programin order to keep learning, improve my skills and finalize my university.

I'm pretty calm, I love coffee, animals and music. I'm a Linux enthusiast and I'll work hard to get CEH certification as soon as possible.

CONTACT INFO

Email: drky@raccoonsolutions.net

GitHub: github.com/drky99
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/drky
Portfolium: raccoonsolutions.net/drky

PERSONAL INTERESTS & HOBBIES

Cybersecurity, Probability & Statistics, Latte Art, Privacy, Crypto, Digital Drawing, Operative Systems, Low Level Programming, Electronics, Blockchain, Fintech, Distrotesting, Graphic Design, Videogames.

EDUCATION

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO DE MÉXICO (2017-Today)

I'm studying Computer Systems Engineering at the Instituto Tecnológico de México campus Morelia, I'm about to finish my 9th semester on the specialization of Cybersecurity.

CISCO NETACAD (2021)

I have a couple of certificades of the program Cisco CCNA Routing and Switching (CCNA R&S) from Cisco Netacad and the Instituto Tecnológico de Morelia. Introduction to routing and switching; and Network Scaling. Also, I have a certificade of Introduction to Cybersecurity by this institute.

PLATZI (2020-2021)

I've taken many of the courses presented by Platzi as a reinforcement of the topics taken at my university, with this courses I enhanced my knowledge on some technologies.

SKILLS

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

Python, JavaScript, Java, C++, PHP, C#, C, Kotlin, SQL, Assembly, TypeScript.

TECHNOLOGIES

Linux, MySQL, MariaDB, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redis, Firebase, Docker, Apache, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, GIT, Android, Raspberry Pi, Arduino.

FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES & TOOLS

React, React-Native, MaterializeCSS, Bootstrap, Ulkit CSS, JWT, Express, Svelte, Laravel, Socker.IO, Sequelize, Material UI, Selenium, jQuery, WordPress, VirtualBox, VMWare, Hyper-V, VMWare EXSI, Packet Tracer, Photoshop, Illustrator, Medibang, Krita, Gimp, Android Studio, Cinema 4D, Cheat Engine, Microsoft Office.

LANGUAGES

Spanish ★ ★ ★ ★
 English ★ ★ ★

EXPERIENCE

IINII (2022-Today)

I'm working as a FullStack developer at IINII on a currently private project. Also, I do the Team Leader role on this project.

Stardeos (2022-Today)

I've been working as volunteer colaborator at Stardeos for a short period of time. On this project I've made optimization and security contributions. Also, I've worked as FullStack developer on this project.

El Tepetate (2019-2020)

As project for the Academic Software Factory of the Instituto Tecnológico de Morelia, we made a web technologies based administration platform for the trout farm El Tepetate. This project took part of a engineering contest on the institution, my team drawn the 1st place with another team.

Administrative Enginieering Master (2021)

As social service project, my classmate and me, made the presentation web page for the Administrative Engineering Master at the Instituto Tecnológico de Morelia